Hey everyone! Welcome to this new video in which I'm going to show you some new goth clubbing outfits
because I want to go to a party in a few weeks. Clubs are opening again and I need some inspiration
so I thought I'm going to take you with me and show you some of the new stuff I have.
I partnered up with Punk Rave Store and I have to check out the different outfits
because I'm not sure what I'm going to wear so I hope I can give you some inspiration too
Thank you.
So this is the first outfit.
I have to say I was really skeptical about this fake fur shrug in the beginning because
it's so not my style.
But I think in combination with the whole outfit it looks really cool and it's so comfortable
and cozy.
So I don't know.
I changed my mind.
It's not that bad.
I admit it.
And overall the outfit is so comfortable because the leggings are really stretchy.
And yeah, I don't know.
The shrug is comfortable.
And I'm...
Yeah, you may think I'm only wearing a bra so it has to be cold.
But I feel completely dressed with the gauntlets here and this shrug which keeps me so warm.
I don't think I would need a jacket for this look.
It's an 8.
I really like this one.
This is a completely shiny object
It's a coat and a bodysuit and over-knee boots and I think this is totally fetish because
I don't know, it's shiny and you have this look here with the boots and the highlights.
So yeah, I totally like the lacing here in the back of the coat and I have to say it
keeps me warm as well.
Gothic fetish outfit, yes totally. I would rate it a 9 out of 10.
Although I would not wear these heels for clubbing.
This coat makes me feel really badass.
I kind of feel like I am a super villain or something in a movie.
Really cool, especially for dancing maybe.
So if it gets too warm, I can do one thing.
I can get rid of the coat.
Yeah, it's a bit more naked of course.
And I doubt I would do this at a normal goth party.
But anyway, this would be fun if there's a pool and you want to jump into the pool.
Let's do the next outfit.
We'll be right back.
Okay, I did not try this outfit before I filmed this video, so it's a bit of a surprise.
And I have to say, I think it's a bit plain compared to the other outfits.
I mean, I like the back of the dress, because it's a bit shiny, and I like the overall style.
Maybe seven, because the dress fits good, although I had to get in over my head, so
it ruined my hair again and it was really hassle to get into but yeah I tried to upgrade
it with some short gloves and with my standard pleaser shoes and I wanna use this opportunity
to talk about shoes and going out because whenever I'm showing like platform boots in
my videos everyone is like oh please wear heels please wear heels and guys sorry to
disappoint you but we're not here to go out just to please your eyes because we
want to be comfortable when we go out and yeah I can understand that you think
these look great for going out or the ones I'm wearing at the moment but to be
honest they're not very comfortable I mean I did it I wore my pleaser for
going out it was okay but if I want to go out and want to have a comfortable
night I'm going to go with these shoes you may think they're ugly you may think
they're a bit brutal but they're so comfortable there's no comparison
between these shoes and the Sleaze-E-Heels for example for a whole night of dancing
and walking in a disco for example my local disco has an outdoor area with
cobblestones. You don't want to walk all evening over cobblestones with really thin heels. So these
are like my favorite shoes to go out. I have a lot of these platform boots because they're
so comfortable and I do like the look. But yeah, just wanted to point that out.
Thank you.
Again, a full PVC outfit and I love the gauntlets, gloves, whatever you may call it.
They're so futuristic somehow, I don't know.
And they're really comfortable.
They may not look like it, but they are.
And I think they upgrade the whole outfit.
But yeah, I like it all in all.
And I'm wearing shoes, which are kind of a compromise
between the plateau boots and the high heels
because they have heels, but they're super comfortable.
So I can dance all night in them as well
without wearing these chunky plateau boots.
Yeah, so I think I would rate this outfit like a 10
because it's super comfortable.
It fits the topic fetish goth clubbing super good.
Although I would need a jacket to go to the party,
which I can hand over there.
And then I would go party like this.
I think this is really funky and really cool clubbing outfit but I'm going to show you one last outfit.
Thank you.
Okay, final outfit.
It's an eyecatcher with this coat.
Or rather cape.
Although I have to say it's quite heavy and it's pulling here at the neck.
So I guess for a night out I would wear this at first to walk around once.
Everybody can see me wearing it.
And then I would probably hand it in at the wardrobe.
I would probably hand it in at the wardrobe.
So I would have only the leggings and the top.
But I like this outfit.
It's so badass again.
I don't know what it is but Pankrage really makes cool clubbing outfits and really impressive outfits.
totally like them. Apparently my arms are one is thicker and one is thinner. Anyway,
I think it's a 9 or rather 8. I don't know, it's not too fetishy again because it's like
a leather look or wet look, yes, but no PVC and it's a coat. Cape is really goth, so it's
rather gothy than fetishy so I don't know I would say like an eight yeah okay so I think my rating
was on point I rate them again like that I think the 10 is really my style and I would love to wear
it out and yeah this one is cool as well can't say that some are more gothy and more more fetish
others anyway um i had fun with this video i had fun showing you all these outfits maybe you can
take some inspiration with you or you can also write a comment and tell me what you like to
wear when you go out leave a comment and a thumbs up and subscribe and all that stuff
also thank you to punk rave store for supporting me again always with these wonderful clothes i
do like them and I do wear them out. Okay see you in the next video. Have a nice time. Bye.